> > Jem Young: 但我对 twitter.com 做了 ping 操作，我没有 ping IP 地址。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: But I pinged twitter.com,
and I didn't ping an IP address.
而工作方式是另一套协议，有很多协议。
And the way that works is another set of
protocols, there's a lot of protocols.
当你看着互联网和那些运行互联网的人
When you look at the Internet and
the people that run the Internet and
有一些人运行因特网或运行交换机和连接，以及
there are people that run the Internet or
run the switches and connections and
骨子里
backbones.
再一次，这是一个信任系统，其中一个是 DNS 系统。
Again, it's this trust system and
one of those things is the DNS system.
DNS 被我想说是 ICANN 因特网我忘了 ICANN 的代表了
DNS is run by I wanna say it's ICANN
Internet, I forgot what ICANN stands for.
它代表什么，不要担心，而是控制域名。
It stands for something, don't worry,
but they control domain names.
当您购买域名时，实际支付一小部分费用 $ 0.60 或
When you buy domain name, you actually
pay a little bit of fee $0.60 or
也许更不适用于 ICANN ，他们帮助创建这个域名系统。
maybe more maybe less to ICANN and
they help create this domain name system.
而它只是一个互联网电话簿。
And what it is is just,
it's an Internet phone book.
但这太简单了
But that's oversimplifying it.
其实是一个智能的网上电话簿，就说哎，
It's actually an intelligent
Internet phone book, just says hey,
我想去 twitter.com
I want to go to twitter.com.
它不一定直接把你路由到旧金山的服务器上
It's not necessarily routing you
directly to the servers in San Francisco
因为那样会很缓慢
because that would be really slow.
世界上到处都有数据中心
There's things called data
centers all around the world,
记录在第二个记录中
which is documented in a second.
但 DNS 说，这个解决的最接近的服务器是什么 ?
But DNS says, what's the closest
server that this resolves to?
所以它所做的就是将域名映射到 IP 地址。
So all it does is it maps
domain names to IP addresses.
我们需要他们因为我不记得自己的 IP 地址
And we need them because I can't
remember my own IP address,
我记不起任何人的 IP 地址我几乎不记得自己的电话号码了
I can't remember anybody's IP address,
I can barely remember my own phone number.
DNS 系统
The DNS system,
你可能已经听说过了，因为这就是互联网的运作方式。
you've probably heard of it because again,
this is how the Internet works.
这就是它如何进入的。
This is how it became accessible.
我们并不都是用电视和电视
We're not all using shells and
using telnet and
所有这些命令行工具下载 Web 页面，我们使用的是 GUIs。
all these command line tools to
download web pages, we're using GUIs.
域名系统只是让更多人使用互联网的一种方式。
Domain name system is just a way of making
the Internet accessible for more people.
你可能都看见了吧
And you probably all see or
not you probably,
我保证你见过域和领域像是 frontendmasters.com
I guarantee you've seen domains and domain
is something like frontendmasters.com,
jemyoung.com 这叫你的域名
jemyoung.com, that's called your domain.
点 com点 biz 点网点点
The dot com, dot biz,
dot net, dot anything,
这是顶级域名，是 TLD。
that's the top level domain, it's the TLD.
TLD 由特定公司，实体或国家或地区拥有。
TLDs are owned by specific companies,
entities or countries.
你知道我最不喜欢的 TLD 是什么吗
You know what my least favorite TLD is?
多特别 你知道的， bot -i-z.
Dot biz.
You know, dot b-i-z.
就好像我看到了点东西
It just seems like if I
see something dot biz,
无意冒犯任何有点 biz TLD 的人它就像是一个骗局
no offense to anybody with a dot biz TLD,
it just seems like a scam.
如果是点 biz 就像 wow.
If it's dot biz, it's like wow.
有个 [INAUDIBLE] 想给你钱而不是点 biz
There's an [INAUDIBLE] that wants
to give money instead of dot biz.
哇不我开玩笑的
Wow, no, I'm kidding.
我真的不别用点 biz
I'm really not, don't use dot biz.
在这几年里如果你没注意到
And over the years,
if you haven't noticed,
所有好的点 coms 都是用的，不一定是真的。
all the good dot coms are taken,
which is not necessarily true.
你只需要得到真正的创造力
You just have to get really,
really creative.
还记得几年前的那个阶段吗
Remember that phase a couple
of years ago with the dot lys?
就像闪动的，迅速的，就像新的一样，像点 li一样。
It was like bitly, fastly, that was
like the hot new thing, like the dot li.
我想在某个国家的某个地方说点歌词
I want to say dot lyzone
by some country somewhere.
我不记得了你可以查清楚
I don't remember, you can look it up.
有点里奥真的很贵
There's dot io, which is really expensive.
我想说拥有这个国家的密克罗尼西亚
I wanna say it's Micronesia
that owns that country, but
几乎每个国家都有自己的顶级域名
almost every country has
their own top level domain.
所以你可以再次说 dmx.ru
So you can say, again, dmx.ru,
dmx 是俄罗斯的谷歌，点 ru 是俄罗斯， cn 是中国。
dmx is the Google of Russia,
dot ru is Russia, cn is China.
但在很大程度上，点 com 仍然是真正的
But largely dot com is still
kind of the domain that really
因为它是 OG 域，第一个域，或者是其中一个原始域。
wants to have because it's the OG domains,
the first one, or one of the originals.
这里有点网，有点组织，但通常是点 orgs，
There's also.dot net, there's dot org,
but generally dot orgs,
它以前是你得不到非盈利性的
it used to be you couldn't get one
without being like a nonprofit status or
或者大学之类的
something like that, or university.
但是他们加了点小点你的很多学院
But they since added dot edu,
which a lot of your colleges or
大学，就像有个点点。
universities, things
like that have a dot edu.
但现在有一大堆顶级域名因为公司很不错
But now there's a whole bunch of top level
domains, because companies are like well,
我怎么无法拥有自己的 TLD 和我的 CANN
how come I can't have my own TLD and
I CANNs like, okay,
我们会为你做些新的
we'll make some new ones for you.
现在，在谷歌的网站上，有点杰夫，有点派对，
So now there's dot Google there's dot dev,
there's dot party,
我最喜欢的域名
my favorite domain name.
只有很多顶级域
Just lots of top level domains, so
好的是如果你今天需要一个网站而你没有
the good thing is if you need a website
today and you don't have one.
你会在一天结束的时候有一个，但是你也可以用任何的 TLD
You're gonna have one by the end of the
day but also you could use whatever TLD
除了点 biz 之外，我告诉你别用点 biz ，这是个坏主意。
you want except for dot biz, I'm telling
you don't use dot biz, this is a bad idea.
子域将是博客或测试或 dev 点。
A subdomain would be the blog or
tests or dev dot something.
这就是所谓的亚域。
That's what's known as a sub domain.
这就意味着它仍会路由到主域，但是
And that just means it still
routes to the main domain, but
这可能只是现场的另一个部分
it's just probably
a different part of the site.
现在，是否有人告诉我为什么要使用子域与路径?
Now, can anybody tell me why I would
use a sub domain versus a path?
而一条路径是真正的 com 斜杠，或者关于我或我
And a path would be genuine com
slash about or about who am I or
就像这样
something like that.
好的萨姆
Yes, Sam.
>> 扬声器 2: 如果要有多个实际的独立服务器。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: If you want to have
more than one actual separate server.
>> Jem Young: 对，对。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah, exactly, right.
>> 扬声器 2: 它允许您更有效地阻止数据交叉
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It allows you to partition
your data more effectively prevents cross
站点脚本编制之类的
site scripting, stuff like that.
> > Jem Young: 是的，你的想法非常好。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah,
you're thinking at a really good level.
对于用户，子域，它仅表示，
For users, the subdomain,
it just indicates,
它是一个不同的地点
it's a different site generally.
因此 blog.jemyoung.com 与 jemyoung.com 完全不同。
So blog.jemyoung.com looks completely
different from jemyoung.com.
我不是在 pimping 我自己的网站，很穷，我不坚持，
And I'm not pimping my own website,
it's pretty poor, I don't maintain it,
我觉得它在跑
I think it's running.
我甚至不知道是否有一半的时间因为你知道
I don't even know if it's running
half the time because you know.
> 演讲者 3: 它正在运行，但是你的最后一个岗位是 5 年前的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: It's running but
your last post was five years ago.
> > Jem Young: 是的，别对我说
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah, don't judge me.
>> [INAUDIBLE] >> Jem Young: 不要法官。
&gt;&gt; [INAUDIBLE]
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Don't judge me.
>> 演讲者 3: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: [LAUGH]
>> Jem Young: 我以为这是
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: I thought this was
一个判断自由的区域
a judgment free zone.
我想，我要成为互联网名，开始做部落格。
I thought hey, I'm going to become
internet famous and start doing a blog.
然后我就跑出来了我不记得我的最后一个职位是
And then I ran out of steam really fast of
off that, I don't remember my last post is
可能是很重要的事
on probably hashing or
something like that so important.
但它只告诉用户你在这个网站的完全不同部分
But it just tells the user that you're at
a completely different part of the site,
它和这个网站的关联，但是它可能完全是一个不同的应用。
and its affiliated with the site, but it's
probably a different application entirely.
第一条路， blog.jemyoung.com 是，是，你是
First the path, blog.jemyoung.com slash
about, which is yeah, you're part of
网站和你就在不同的路径上，在主网站上是不同的页面。
the site and you're just on a different
route, a different page on the main site.
而由于 DNS 系统，我可以映射 jemyoung.com 。
And because of DNS system,
I can map jemyoung.com, the 23.23.185.61.
所以别忘了每次我都能把它输入
So rather than remember that every
single time, I can just type that in and
DNS 解析程序会发现的
the DNS resolvers figure that out.
他们怎么想出来的
How do they figure that out?
更多服务器。
More servers.
有很多服务器。
There are a lot of servers.
因特网建立在服务器，信任和节点以及类似的东西上。
The Internet is built on servers and
trusts and nodes and things like that.
但有一个叫名称服务器的想法。
But there's idea called a name server.
名称服务器是保留该映射的实际实体。
And the name server is the actual
entity that keeps that mapping.
因此，每当您从我们的 Web 主机购买新域时，请使用名称羊或
So whenever you buy a new domain
from our web host, so name sheep or
去爸爸或者谷歌还有一个大的
Go Daddy or Google and
one of the big ones.
他们都有名字的服务器
They all have name servers.
就这样说，这个人刚刚买了这个域名。
And that just says hey,
this person just bought this domain.
而且可能哪儿也不去
And it's probably not going anywhere.
但如果你需要查清楚我就知道那是什么地方
But if you need to look it up,
I know exactly where that is.
实际上，我将会用分组的方式来谈论这个问题。
And actually, I'll talk about
that a second with packets.
但名字是我们可能不知道的
But names are the thing that
we probably don't know exist.
我们今天要修改一下因为我们要用它来说明
We're going to modify one today just
because we're going to use it to point
从我们的主机到我们的服务器
from our hosts to our
server at some point.
但知道这些名字服务器的存在是件好事。
But it's good to know
that name servers exists.
他们本质上是网络的记录员
They essentially Are they the record
keepers of the internet if you're trying
以输入域名
to type them domain name